<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SanDiegoGuideApp</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="places">SCENES</string>
    <string name="restaurants">FOODS</string>
    <string name="events">EVENTS</string>
    <string name="artist">ARTISTS</string>


    <!--BALBOA-->
    <string name="balboa_park_title">BALBOA PARK</string>
    <string name="balboa_park_description">
"Balboa Park is a 1,200-acre (490 ha) urban cultural park in San Diego, California, United States.[3]\
In addition to open space areas, natural vegetation zones, green belts\
gardens, and walking paths, it contains museums, several theaters\
, and the world-famous San Diego Zoo.There are also many recreational facilities and\
several gift shops and restaurants within the boundaries of the park.\
Placed in reserve in 1835, the park's site is one of the\
oldest in the United States dedicated\
to public recreational use. Balboa Park is managed and maintained by the\
Parks and Recreation Department of the City of San Diego."\
    </string>

    <!--SAN DIEGO ZOO-->
    <string name="san_diego_zoo_title">SAN DIEGO ZOO</string>
    <string name="san_diego_zoo_description">"The San Diego Zoo is a zoo in Balboa Park, San Diego,\
California, housing over 3,700 animals of more than 650 species and subspecies.\
[1] Its parent organization, San Diego Zoo Global, is one of the largest[better source needed]\
zoological membership associations in the world, with more than 250,000 member households\
and 130,000 child memberships, representing more than a half million people.\
[6] The San Diego Zoo was a pioneer in the concept of open-air,\
cageless exhibits that re-create natural animal habitats."</string>

    <!--SEAWORLD-->
    <string name="seaworld">Seaworld San Diego</string>
    <string name="seaworld_san_diego_description">"SeaWorld San Diego is an animal theme park,\
oceanarium, outside aquarium, and marine mammal park, located in San Diego,\
California, United States." </string>


    <!--SEAWORLD-->
    <string name="coronado">Coronado Beach</string>
    <string name="coronado_description">"Coronado, also known as Coronado Island,\
is a resort city located in San Diego County, California, across and around San Diego Bay\
from downtown San Diego.[8] Its population was 24,697 at the 2010 census,\
[5][6] up from 24,100 at the 2000 census. It is part of the San Diego County, California."
    </string>

    /*Retaurant Sections */

    <!--CRAB_HUT-->
    <string name="crab_hut">Crab Hut</string>
    <string name="crab_hut_description">"Crab Hut was founded in 2007 by a family that loves food\
and beer, with one purpose to bring San Diego some good ole' Southern sass and flavor.\
Our goal is to redefine the eating out experience and engaging the guest with hands on food,\
while keeping it fresh with products grown and rise locally here in San Diego. "
    </string>


    <!--Sushi Ota-->
    <string name="sushi_ota">Sushi Ota</string>
    <string name="sushi_ota_description">"Crab Hut was founded in 2007 by a family that loves food\
and beer, with one purpose to bring San Diego some good ole' Southern sass and flavor.\
Our goal is to redefine the eating out experience and engaging the guest with hands on food,\
while keeping it fresh with products grown and rise locally here in San Diego. "
    </string>




    <string name="buga_bbq">Buga BBQ</string>
    <string name="buga_bbq_description">"At Buga Korean BBQ Restaurant,\
we serve a range of food and beverage items, choose from our delectable selection of various \
high-quality beef, chicken, pork or seafood, then cook it on our state of the art grills, right at your table.\"
    </string>

    <!--Del-mar Fair-->
    <string name="delmar_fair">DelMar Fair</string>
    <string name="delmar_fair_description">"Did you know San Diego is home to the largest county fair in the United States?\
Every summer, more than 1.6 million visitors flock to the local attraction.\
For many, the annual fair is a family tradition —\
a familiar place to gather to learn, eat, ride, watch, dance and most of all, to participate!"
    </string>

    <!--Del-mar Fair-->
    <string name="comic_con">Comic Con</string>
    <string name="comic_con_description">"Comic-Con International: San Diego began in 1970 when a group of comics,\
movie, and science fiction fans -- including the late Shel Dorf, Ken Krueger, and Richard Alf\
-- banded together to put on the first comic book convention in southern California."
    </string>

    <!--Iron Butterfly-->
    <string name="iron_butterfly">Iron Butterfly</string>
    <string name="iron_butterfly_description">Iron Butterfly is an American rock band best known for the 1968 hit "In-A-Gadda-Da-Vida",\
providing a dramatic sound that led the way towards the development of hard rock and heavy metal music.\
    </string>

    <!--Drive Like Jehu-->
    <string name="drive_like_jehu">Drive Like Jehu</string>
    <string name="drive_like_jehu_description">"Drive Like Jehu is an American post-hardcore band from San Diego active from 1990 to 1995
Formed by rhythm guitarist and vocalist Rick Froberg and lead guitarist John Reis following the breakup of their band Pitchfork,\
the band's lineup also included bassist Mike Kennedy and drummer Mark Trombino."
    </string>




</resources>
